✔ actual UI transitive package keeps its real upstream version (0.9573ms)
✔ backend Jest dependency chain uses the same patched braces package (4.5863ms)
✔ normal glob, nested alternatives, ranges and escaped braces keep behavior (1.4717ms)
✔ parse rejects deep balanced and unbalanced braces/parentheses without stack overflow (0.638ms)
✔ compile rejects deep balanced and unbalanced braces/parentheses without stack overflow (0.5754ms)
✔ expand rejects deep balanced and unbalanced braces/parentheses without stack overflow (1.1809ms)
✔ stringify rejects deep balanced and unbalanced braces/parentheses without stack overflow (0.453ms)
✔ compile also validates externally supplied AST depth, width and cycles (1.6503ms)
✔ expand also validates externally supplied AST depth, width and cycles (1.0854ms)
✔ stringify also validates externally supplied AST depth, width and cycles (0.4353ms)
ℹ tests 10
ℹ suites 0
ℹ pass 10
ℹ fail 0
ℹ cancelled 0
ℹ skipped 0
ℹ todo 0
ℹ duration_ms 88.2587
